- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[accordion music]
[手风琴音乐]
♪ ♪
- Oh, thanks for the ride,
Dylan.
-哦，谢谢你的搭车，
迪伦.
- No problem, Pearl.
- 没问题，珀尔。
You still down
for that party tonight?
你还是低落
今晚参加那个聚会吗？
- [gasping]
Oh, you bet!
- [喘气]
哦，你打赌！
- Nautical.
I'll pick you up at eight.
- 航海。
我八点来接你。
- Ooooh...
- 噢...
[swooning sounds]
[昏厥的声音]
[record scratch]
[记录刮痕]
- Again?
Come on, Pearly girl,
- 再次？
来吧，珍珠女孩，
we're running low
on doors here.
我们所剩无几了
在这里的门上。
- Oh, I'm sorry daddy.
I'm just so excited to go
- 哦，对不起，爸爸。
我很兴奋要去
to the big party tonight,
I, I just--
今晚的盛大聚会，
我，我只是——
- Oh no!
No no no no no no no no no.
- 哦不！
不不不不不不不不不。
Sorry sweetie, Daddy's
going out to play cards
对不起亲爱的，爸爸的
出去打牌
with the boys tonight.
今晚和孩子们在一起。
[cha-ching]
[查清]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
- But, but daddy!
- 但是，但是爸爸！
- No buts!
I can't be worrying
- 没有但是！
我不能担心
about you
all night, honey.
关于你
整个晚上，亲爱的。
- [sniffling]
- [抽鼻子]
But daddy, I want
to go to the party!
但爸爸，我想要
去参加聚会！
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- Oh shrimp.
- 噢，虾。
-[blubbering]
-[哭泣]
- Whoa!
- 哇！
- [Pearl sobs]
[buzz saw spinning]
- [珍珠抽泣]
[圆锯旋转]
[clock cuckooing]
[时钟咕咕声]
- [Krabs whimpering]
- [Pearl cries]
- [螃蟹呜咽]
- [珍珠哭泣]
- Whew.
Hmm?
- 呼。
唔？
- Aaah!
- 啊啊！
There, there,
me little beluga.
那里，那里，
我小白鲸。
It'll be okay.
会没事的。
I hired Mr. Squidward
to baby-sit!
我雇佣了章鱼哥先生
去照顾孩子！
Just like when
you were little.
就像当
你还小。
[camera clicks]
[相机点击]
- Ew, Dad!
Squidward is so lame!
- 呃，爸爸！
章鱼哥太蹩脚了！
- Lame-shmame!
- 蹩脚的！
You and Squidward
will have so much fun,
你和章鱼哥
将会有很多乐趣，
You won't want
to go anywhere!
你不会想要
去任何地方！
But just in case...
但以防万一...
[alarm blares]
[警报声]
- you won't be able
to go anywhere!
-你不能
去任何地方！
[laughing]
[笑]
[knocking on door]
Oh! Just in time.
[敲门]
哦！恰逢其时。
- Mm-hmm.
Hmm?
- 嗯嗯。
唔？
[buzzer blares]
Hmm?
[蜂鸣器鸣响]
嗯？
- Squidward!
Thanks for keeping an eye
- 章鱼哥！
感谢您的关注
on me little
Pearl tonight.
对我来说很少
今晚珍珠。
- No problem.
- 没问题。
- Remember our deal,
Squidward:
- 记住我们的协议，
章鱼哥：
Keep Pearl
out of trouble,
保留珍珠
摆脱困境，
and I'll give you
one shift a week
我会给你
每周一班
without SpongeBob.
没有海绵宝宝。
But if anything happens
to my little angel...
但如果有什么事情发生
致我的小天使...
[screams]
[annoying laughter]
[尖叫声]
[烦人的笑声]
- No, please!
Anything but that!
- 不，拜托！
除了那个之外什么都可以！
Don't worry, Mr. Krabs.
You can count on me.
别担心，蟹老板。
你可以信赖我。
- I knew I could.
- 我知道我可以。
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
- Phew.
- Oh thanks for watching
- 唷。
- 哦，谢谢您的观看
the house tonight,
Squidward.
今晚的房子，
章鱼哥。
I'll be back late, so
y'know don't wait up for me!
我会晚点回来，所以
你知道别等我！
- [grunting]
Your dad said we have
- [咕哝]
你爸爸说我们有
to stay in tonight...
[grunting]
今晚要留在...
[咕噜声]
But that doesn't
mean we can't have...
但这并不
意味着我们不能...
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Fun!
乐趣！
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
- Look, we could play with
this Cetaceous Sally doll.
- 看，我们可以一起玩
这个鲸类莎莉娃娃。
Or we could color
this princess coloring book.
或者我们可以上色
这本公主图画书。
Or we could
sing along with--
或者我们可以
跟着唱——
Aaah!
啊啊！
[gasps]
Sally!
[喘气]
莎莉！
Aaaaah!
啊啊啊！
Outside the lines.
线外。
[cringing]
[畏缩]
Hmm.
唔。
Pearl?
珍珠？
Hello?
你好？
Hmm.
Hey, uh, Pearl...
唔。
嘿，呃，珍珠……
Ummm...
嗯...
Whatcha up to?
到底在忙什么？
- Arts and crafts.
- 艺术和手工艺。
- Hey, I dabble
in the arts myself.
- 嘿，我涉足
我自己在艺术方面。
Maybe I could help!
也许我可以帮忙！
[evil laugh]
[邪恶的笑声]
- [yelps]
Uh never mind, I--
- [尖叫声]
呃，没关系，我——
You seem to have
that under control.
你似乎有
一切都在控制之中。
I'll just, um, be out here
if you need me.
我就，嗯，就在这里
如果你需要我。
Or not.
Preferably not.
或不。
最好不是。
That is one morbid teen.
那是一个病态的青少年。
That ought to keep him
out of my hair.
这应该让他
从我的头发里出来。
[horn honks]
Hmm?
[喇叭鸣响]
嗯？
[groovy music]
[动听的音乐]
[horn honking]
[喇叭鸣响]
It's go time!
出发时间到了！
[snoring]
[打鼾]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
[snickering]
[窃笑]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
- [yelping]
Oh!
- [尖叫]
哦！
What's happening?
发生什么事了？
Pearl?
珍珠？
Oh.
You asleep?
哦。
你睡着了吗？
Aww, she must have
tuckered herself out.
哇，她一定有
她把自己蜷缩起来。
Aah!
Oh, no!
啊啊！
哦，不！
Maybe if we get it on ice
they can reattach it!
也许如果我们把它放在冰上
他们可以重新连接它！
[yelping]
[尖叫]
[muffled screaming]
[低沉的尖叫声]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[gasping for breath]
[喘气]
Aaah.
啊啊。
- Oh thanks for
the ride, Dylan.
- 哦，谢谢
骑行，迪伦。
- No prob.
- 没问题。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
She's gone!
Krabs is gonna kill me!
她走了！
螃蟹要杀了我！
[playful accordion music]
[俏皮的手风琴音乐]
♪ ♪
- Um, that sign
said "surface."
- 嗯，那个标志
说“表面”。
Are you sure
this is the way?
你确定吗
这是路吗？
- For sure, babe.
We're going to
- 当然，宝贝。
我们要去
a breach party.
违约方。
- Oh, I've never been
to one of those before.
-哦，我从来没有去过
到之前的其中之一。
Sounds exciting.
听起来很令人兴奋。
[tires peel out]
[轮胎剥落]
- Whoo!
- 呼！
- Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
- 嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯。
[tires screeching]
[轮胎的尖叫声]
Hmm.
Still warm.
唔。
还是温暖的。
The surface, eh?
表面，嗯？
That SpongeBob-free
shift will be mine!
没有海绵宝宝
转变将是我的！
[huffing and puffing]
[气喘吁吁]
Aaaah!
啊啊啊！
[groaning]
[呻吟]
SpongeBob...shift...mine...
海绵宝宝……变身……我的……
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- [swooning]
- [昏厥]
[munching]
[咀嚼]
Mmm, oh Dylan.
嗯，哦迪伦。
All: Chug, chug, chug, chug!
全体：嘎嘎，嘎嘎，嘎嘎，嘎嘎！
All: Breach, breach, breach,
breach, breach, breach--
全部：违规，违规，违规，
违规、违规、违规——
- [burps]
- [打嗝]
[satisfying moan]
[满足的呻吟声]
All: Whoo-hoo!
全体：呼呼！
[groovy music playing]
[美妙的音乐演奏]
[party chatter]
[聚会闲聊]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[gasping]
[喘气]
Pearl!
珍珠！
[all gasping]
[全都喘气]
- You have to
come home, right away!
- 你必须
回家吧，马上！
We can do whatever
you want if we go back now!
我们可以做任何事
你要我们现在就回去吧！
I'll even play
you some jazz!
我什至会玩
你来点爵士乐吧！
Kids love jazz!
孩子们喜欢爵士乐！
[screeching flute]
[all groaning]
[尖叫的长笛]
[全都呻吟]
♪ Come on Pearl,
let's go home ♪
♪ 来吧，珍珠，
我们回家吧♪
♪ I can't leave here
all alone ♪
♪ 我不能离开这里
独自一人♪
♪ Let's get back
before your dad... ♪
♪ 我们回去吧
在你爸爸面前……♪
[scatting]
[分散]
- No!
- Jazz...making me...nerdier!
- 不！
- 爵士乐...让我...变得更书呆子！
[both groaning]
[两人都呻吟]
[flute screeching]
[长笛尖叫]
- Oh, this is
so embarrassing!
- 哦，这是
太尴尬了！
- Forget him Pearl,
let's breach.
- 忘了他吧，珍珠，
让我们突破吧。
[all cheering]
[大家欢呼]
- Aaah!
- 啊啊！
Yeah!
是的！
[all cheering]
[大家欢呼]
- I don't know.
Is it dangerous?
- 我不知道。
危险吗？
- Uh-uh, babe.
It's nautical.
- 呃呃，宝贝。
这是航海的。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
[swooning]
[昏厥]
- Pearl!
- 珍珠！
What about yo-yos?
溜溜球呢？
Kids love yo-yo--
孩子们喜欢溜溜球——
Oof!
钱币！
- Okay, let's do it!
- 好吧，我们开始吧！
One...two...three...
一二三...
Yahoo!
雅虎！
This is so coral!
这太珊瑚了！
Oof!
钱币！
[gasping]
[喘气]
Dylan, help!
迪伦，救命啊！
This isn't nautical!
这不是航海！
- Oh man, she's beached.
- 天哪，她已经搁浅了。
- We're gonna be
in so much trouble!
- 我们会是
遇到这么多麻烦！
- Leave her!
Let's cheese it!
- 离开她！
让我们干酪吧！
- Let's get out of here.
- [grunting]
- 我们离开这里吧。
- [咕哝]
Oh, no!
哦，不！
- Pearl!
Are you all right?
- 珍珠！
你还好吗？
- Oh, Squidward, I'm so sorry
I didn't listen to you!
-哦，章鱼哥，我很抱歉
我没听你的！
- It's okay.
- 没关系。
Let's just get you
out of here.
让我们来接你吧
离开这里。
[straining]
[紧张]
Oof!
钱币！
[muffled grunting]
[低沉的咕噜声]
Oh.
哦。
Okay, okay.
Just, hold on a second.
好吧，好吧。
只是，等一下。
- Hold on?
What are you--
- 坚持，稍等？
你是做什么的 -
Gah.
嘎。
- [huffing]
- [气喘吁吁]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Aaah.
啊啊。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Huh?
- 啊？
[burps and yells]
[打嗝和叫喊]
Aaaah!
啊啊啊！
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
I can't believe Dylan
ditched me.
我不敢相信迪伦
抛弃了我。
My life is over.
我的生命结束了。
- Oh, I don't think
it's that bad.
- 哦，我不认为
太糟糕了。
- Aaah.
- 啊啊。
[piercing sound]
[刺耳的声音]
- I'll um, just get you home.
- 我会，嗯，送你回家。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Narrator:
Many, many minutes later...
旁白：
很多很多分钟之后……
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
Oh.
哦。
- [sighs]
Guess I'll just wait
- [叹气]
我想我只会等待
for my dad to get home.
为了让我爸爸回家。
- Ya know, there is a way
we could still have
- 你知道，有办法
我们仍然可以拥有
a little
fun tonight.
一点
今晚很有趣。
- Really?
- 真的吗？
[both snickering]
[两人窃笑]
[doorbell ringing]
[门铃响]
- Like, hello?
- 就像，你好？
Hmm?
Huh?
唔？
啊？
[annoying laughter]
- Aaah!
[烦人的笑声]
- 啊啊！
[SpongeBob laughs,
Dylan screams]
[海绵宝宝笑了，
迪伦尖叫]
[both snickering]
[两人窃笑]
[ukulele music]
[尤克里里音乐]
♪ ♪
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
♪ ♪
Ya-bow.
雅-鞠躬。
Delivery--
Whoa!
发货--
哇！
Whaaa!
哇啊！
Oof!
钱币！
Delivery.
送货。
- Will you ever learn
how to use those doors?
- 你会学习吗
如何使用这些门？
- Never.
- 绝不。
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
[elevator dings]
[电梯叮叮声]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
Hmm.
唔。
- Has anybody seen
my delivery?
- 有谁看过吗
我的交货？
Delivery coming.
送货来了。
- Huh?
- 啊？
- Pardon me.
- Whoa!
- 请原谅我。
- 哇！
- Hey!
- Oof.
- 嘿！
- 噢。
- Oh, I've heard of this.
Davey Jones' cubicle.
- 哦，我听说过这个。
戴维·琼斯的小隔间。
[yells]
[喊叫]
[SpongeBob groans]
- [gasps]
[海绵宝宝呻吟]
- [喘气]
- Your delivery, ma'am.
- 您的送货，女士。
[stammering]
Whoa, whoa!
[结巴]
哇哦！
Ah.
啊。
Phew.
唷。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Oh, no.
哦，不。
A delicious
Krusty Krab disaster.
一个美味的
蟹堡王灾难。
Call the shore patrol.
Get an ambulance.
呼叫岸边巡逻队。
叫辆救护车。
Does anyone know CSR?
Chocolate Shake Resuscitation.
有人了解企业社会责任吗？
巧克力奶昔复苏。
[squishing]
[压扁]
- It's all right.
Just leave it.
- 没关系。
就留下它吧。
- Here, you can
drink it from here!
- 在这里，你可以
从这里喝吧！
See?
[slurps]
看？
[啜饮]
Yow.
哟。
It's too late.
I did all I could
太晚了。
我已经尽力了
but it wasn't enough.
但这还不够。
I'll just clean up
the remains.
我只会清理
遗骸。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
- Enough.
- 足够的。
Just go.
I'm busy.
走吧。
我很忙。
- In ancient times
one would fall on their sword
- 在古代
有人会倒在他们的剑上
by way of apology.
以道歉的方式。
We at the Krusty Krab
keep that tradition.
我们在蟹堡王
保持这个传统。
[slicing sound, groans]
[切割声、呻吟声]
And now that
that's out of the way,
现在那
那不碍事
I am going to give you
我要给你
the Krusty Krab Customer
Service Pledge of Satisfaction.
蟹堡王顾客
满意服务承诺。
I pledge to come back
here tonight,
我保证会回来
今晚在这里，
and clean this carpet
and make it shine.
并清洁这块地毯
并让它闪闪发光。
As a matter of fact,
I'll clean all your offices
事实上，
我会打扫你所有的办公室
and all your cubicles.
Courtesy of The Krusty Krab.
以及你所有的小隔间。
由蟹堡王提供。
- There's no need.
We have a cleaning robot
- 没必要。
我们有一个清洁机器人
that does that all at night.
整个晚上都是这样。
- No, mom,
I'm not double checking
- 不，妈妈，
我没有双重检查
that the doors are locked.
门是锁着的。
Stop nagging me.
别再唠叨我了。
[indistinct chatter]
- I love you too.
[模糊的喋喋不休]
- 我也爱你。
- Thanks for loaning me
your cleaning cart, Patrick.
- 谢谢你借给我
你的清洁车，帕特里克。
- [munching, grunting]
Cleaning cart?
- [咀嚼，咕噜声]
清洁车？
I thought this was
a food cart?
我以为这是
食品车？
[both yelling]
The best door ever!
[两人大喊]
有史以来最好的门！
Together: Whaaa!
一起：哇啊！
- Hold on.
- 坚持，稍等。
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
- Trash.
- 垃圾。
[burps]
[打嗝]
[beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
[both yelling]
[两人大喊]
- Aaah!
Paper shredder!
- 啊啊！
碎纸机！
[shredding sounds]
[撕碎声]
[gasps]
[喘气]
Ah.
啊。
No two shreds are alike.
没有两片碎片是相同的。
- Let's start here
and make our way
- 让我们从这里开始
并让路
to the milkshake stain.
到奶昔污渍。
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
[groaning, grunting]
[呻吟，咕哝]
I got it.
我得到了它。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[electricity crackling]
[电力噼啪声]
♪ Working guy,
working guy ♪
♪ 上班族，
上班族♪
♪ Working guy, working guy ♪
♪ 工作人员，工作人员 ♪
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[elevator dings]
[电梯叮叮声]
[beeping]
Trash.
[嘟嘟声]
垃圾。
Trash.
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Trash.
垃圾。
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
[burps]
[打嗝]
Trash.
垃圾。
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
- [gleefully yelling]
- [高兴地大喊]
Oh.
哦。
- Hm.
- 嗯。
- Can I just say oops.
- 我可以说哎呀吗？
- Not a problem.
We'll just put them all back up
- 没问题。
我们会把它们全部备份起来
the way they were.
他们本来的样子。
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
- There.
Good as new.
- 那里。
完好如新。
- Uh...
- 呃...
How do we get out of here?
我们怎样才能离开这里？
- Uh, maybe this way?
- 呃，也许是这样？
Oh, or, uh, this way.
哦，或者，呃，这边走。
[videogame music,
both grunting]
[电子游戏音乐，
两人都咕哝着]
Oop, missed one.
Huh--
哎呀，漏了一个。
呃——
- Trash.
- 垃圾。
- Hey, that's mine.
- 嘿，那是我的。
I'm cleaning these offices.
[grunts]
我正在打扫这些办公室。
[咕哝]
- [growls]
- Patrick, catch.
- [咆哮]
- 帕特里克，接住。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [groans]
- [buzzing, beeping]
- [呻吟]
- [嗡嗡声，嘟嘟声]
Trash.
垃圾。
[saw buzzing]
- No!
[看到嗡嗡声]
- 不！
- Run!
- 跑步！
[both yelling, grunting]
[两人都大喊大叫，咕哝着]
[saw cutting]
[锯切]
[both breathing heavy]
[两人呼吸粗重]
[yelling]
[大喊]
- [grunting]
[saw cutting]
- [咕哝]
[锯切]
- Grrr.
- 呃。
- Ugh.
- Boo boo.
- 嘘嘘。
[digital beeping]
[数字蜂鸣声]
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
[both yelling]
[两人大喊]
- Oh, no.
I'm bleeding.
- 哦，不。
我在流血。
It's okay.
It's decaf.
没关系。
它不含咖啡因。
- [moaning]
- [呻吟]
- Trash, trash, trash.
- 垃圾，垃圾，垃圾。
- SpongeBob, why is
this happening?
- 海绵宝宝，为什么
这发生了？
- Trash, trash,
trash, trash, trash.
- 垃圾，垃圾，
垃圾，垃圾，垃圾。
[whimpering]
[whirring, beeping]
[呜咽]
[呼呼声，嘟嘟声]
Trash.
垃圾。
- Um, you--look,
you garbage-can thing.
- 嗯，你——看，
你这个垃圾桶东西。
I don't know
what we did to you
我不知道
我们对你做了什么
but I made a Krusty Krab pledge
to your boss
但我做出了蟹堡王的承诺
给你的老板
to clean these offices.
清洁这些办公室。
[beeping, whirring]
- Oh!
[嘟嘟声，呼呼声]
- 哦！
[groaning]
[呻吟]
- Whoa.
- 哇哦。
Ow!
My rump is roasting.
噢！
我的臀部在烤。
- Hey!
Patrick may be trashy...
- 嘿！
帕特里克可能很垃圾……
- [burps]
- [打嗝]
- But he's not trash.
- 但他不是垃圾。
[yelling, whimpering]
[大喊大叫，呜咽]
- Whoa.
Oh.
- 哇哦。
哦。
[SpongeBob yelling]
- [sighs]
[海绵宝宝大喊大叫]
- [叹气]
Hmm?
唔？
Mmm, Patrick soup.
嗯，帕特里克汤。
- [grunting, yelling]
- [咕哝，大喊]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
- 哇，哇，哇，
哇，哇，哇！
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
哇，哇，哇，
哇，哇，哇！
[thudding]
[重击]
[groans]
[呻吟]
Sorry to do this.
But you'll have to stay here
很抱歉这样做。
但你必须留在这里
until we finish cleaning.
直到我们完成清洁工作。
Here.
This should tide you over
这里。
这应该能让你渡过难关
till we're done.
直到我们完成。
- [burps]
- [打嗝]
- Whew.
Finally.
- 呼。
最后。
Patrick, meet
the main stain that I disdain.
帕特里克，见面吧
我所鄙视的主要污点。
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- Oh, what do you know.
- 哦，你知道什么。
This cleaner contains
saliva enzymes
该清洁剂含有
唾液酶
that break down
chocolate particles.
崩溃的
巧克力颗粒。
Hmm.
You know if we wanted to
唔。
你知道我们是否愿意
we could just--
我们可以——
- [slurping, licking]
- [吸食，舔]
Way ahead of ya.
远远领先于你。
- Make room.
- 腾出空间。
[both licking, slurping]
[都舔，吸吮]
[pounding]
Huh?
[重击]
啊？
[both licking, slurping]
[都舔，吸吮]
[pounding]
[重击]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[whirring, whizzing]
[呼呼，呼呼]
- Eliminate intruders.
- 消灭入侵者。
[beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
- [slurping]
- [发出声音]
[gulps]
[吞咽]
[yelps]
Ew.
[尖叫声]
呃。
Patrick,
stop sweating on me.
帕特里克，
别再为我出汗了。
- I ran out of sweat
an hour ago.
- 我已经流汗了
一小时前。
[beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
both: Aah!
Coffee killer!
两人：啊啊！
咖啡杀手！
[plane whizzing]
[飞机呼啸]
[both yelling]
[两人大喊]
[beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
- You again.
- 又是你。
- Oh, good.
Soda.
- 哦，很好。
苏打。
I was getting
thirsty again.
我正在得到
又渴了。
Aaah.
啊啊。
[grunting, yelling]
[咕哝，大喊]
- This is not refreshing.
- 这并不令人耳目一新。
Ow, oh.
噢，噢。
- Grrr.
- 呃。
Gah.
嘎。
[explosion]
[爆炸]
[electronic buzzing]
[电子嗡嗡声]
- Aaah.
- 啊啊。
Whoa.
哇哦。
[groaning, grunting]
[呻吟，咕哝]
[painful yelling]
[痛苦的叫喊]
- Man, you do not
take a bad picture.
- 伙计，你不
拍一张不好的照片。
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
[muffled groaning]
[低沉的呻吟声]
- Hang in there, buddy.
- 坚持住，伙计。
Hang in there.
坚持住。
[panicked whimpering]
[惊慌的呜咽声]
[sighs]
[叹气]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- [happy yell]
- [高兴地大喊]
- Hey, where'd you get
the tank, Patrick?
- 嘿，你从哪里来的
坦克，帕特里克？
- It's what this company makes:
Tanks.
- 这就是这家公司生产的产品：
坦克。
- How did I not notice that?
- 我怎么没注意到？
We'll use these
as ammunition.
我们将使用这些
作为弹药。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
♪ ♪
- Retreat.
Retreat.
- 撤退。
撤退。
[muffled groans]
[低沉的呻吟声]
Huh?
啊？
- Hello.
- 你好。
[electronic whirring, buzzing]
[电子呼呼声、嗡嗡声]
- Hey Trash Bot.
- 嘿垃圾机器人。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [burps]
- [打嗝]
Mmm.
Trash.
嗯。
垃圾。
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
- SpongeBob SquarePants
always keeps his word.
- 海绵宝宝
总是信守诺言。
That carpet is clean.
那块地毯很干净。
- And I helped.
- 我也帮忙了。
- You sure did, buddy.
- 你确实做到了，伙计。
Come on, pal,
let's go get us a snack.
来吧，朋友，
我们去买点零食吧。
- Oh, I like that sound,
SpongeBob.
- 哦，我喜欢那个声音，
海绵宝宝。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
[hums]
[哼哼]
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
Ah!
啊!
- Ugh.
- I quit.
- 呃。
- 我不干了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪